Previously on 90210...
Adrianna was so worried this
morning when she saw Vanessa,
she told me everything.
Stop pretending you don't know she's back.
You were on your way to meet her.
I can't let you do that.
You'll be traveling in this.
You're gonna put me in a box?
If you won't let me protect you,
you leave me no other choice.
How long have you been staying in L.A.?
I'm just here for a job interview.
So, you're moving here.
I don't know if it's gonna pan out.
I mean, I got to meet you.
I can't take away your
only chance to have a baby.
Mr. Montgomery stipulated
you hire a third party
to carry the child.
There is one other
candidate. Shane has a sister.
You have to be so incredibly brave
to trust somebody you just
met to carry your baby.
I'd really like the
chance to be that person.
- Hey, Silver.
- Hey.
I will do whatever it takes
to get out of your contract
and out of your life.
I was going to release you
so you could work with him without me.
I'm done. Okay? You're released.
- Yo.
Is there a reason why
you're taking apart my sink?
Annie invested 200 grand
into my record label,
and I spent it all on startup costs.
But then I dropped Ade,
which means I have no artist,
no income, no way to pay my sister back.
Since Annie's living here,
I figured I'd fix the
sink so she doesn't think
of her brother as some great, big loser.
Wouldn't it be easier
just to sign a new artist?
No established artist wants
to sign with me right now.
And all the big labels are
taking all the new ones.
So, basically, I'm screwed.
Can I help?
Can you sing?
I meant with the sink.
Yeah, apparently record
labels aren't the only thing
I can't figure out. (chuckles)
Hand me that wrench.
Here.
And, uh... here. What are...
This doesn't even...
Whoa-oh.
Is this a subpoena?
Yeah, it's no big deal.
I've got to go to court tomorrow
to testify at Ashley's preliminary hearing.
You're testifying against
the lady that kidnapped you?
That's kind of heavy.
Are you okay?
(sighs) I'm fine.
Once I testify, this
whole thing will be over,
I never have to think
about the kidnapping again,
and my life can get
finally get back to normal.
Done.
Well, if you need a ride
down to the courthouse,
I'm your man. I have nothing but time.
Nah, I'm actually good.
I'm going to go with Adrianna.
She's got to be down
there anyway for her...
wardrobe malfunction.
Yeah, tell her to plead insanity.
(wry laugh)
(sighs)
Thank you for letting me go
through your closet, Silver.
I can't believe that they're charging me
with indecent exposure.
I need something to wear
in court that screams
"I'm not a sex criminal."
All of my non-slutty clothes are
probably on the left-hand side.
I knew flashing a stadium full of people
at a charity event would impact my career,
but I had no idea it was
going to become my trademark.
I haven't been able to book
a gig since it happened.
And every time I talk to someone,
I feel like they're imagining
me with my shirt off.
I'm sorry, I really would love to talk
but I have to bolt.
I'm supposed to pick up
Michaela in, like, five minutes,
and show her around C.U.
Michaela?
Oh, your surrogate.
And Shane's sister. Weird, I know.
Teddy and I are splitting the living costs,
but I have to oversee everything else:
her doctor's appointments, her housing,
her diet, her exercise.
It's super overwhelming,
and I can't talk right now.
But help yourself to anything in the closet
and we'll totally catch up later.
(door closes)
Shirazi.
Dude, finals week sucks.
All of our extracurricular
activities are on hold,
so I don't get to watch your
buddy Liam pound anybody.
(chuckle)
You going to Finals Frolic tomorrow?
There's going to be plenty of women,
Battle of the Bands.
Yeah, maybe.
I just have to get through this exam first.
Oh, please, God.
Don't sweat it, you're gonna do fine.
Yeah, I wish I had your confidence.
Calculus is not my best subject.
Navid, you are a member
of the Cronus Society.
Everything is our best subject.
Just don't forget to leave
your phone on, all right?
Why?
In case I have to call with
more party info or something.
- See ya, bud.
- See ya.
So this is C.U.
Teddy said you were a
semester away from graduating,
so I figured we could sign
you up with some classes.
Obviously nothing too crazy,
because I don't think an all-nighter would
be good for the baby.
Actually, school's kind
of more my family's thing.
That's why I was so
excited to get this job.
I get to move to L.A.,
meet a bunch of cool people.
Yeah, meet a bunch of cool
people, that will happen.
Maybe while you're pregnant though,
you'll want to learn something. Right?
Navid.
This is Michaela, remember?
Oh, yeah.
We met at, uh, Dixon's place.
- Yeah.
- How's it going?
It's great.
I'm going to go grab a course book.
Just in case.
I'll be right back.
Hey, look, thanks for not saying anything,
about us hooking up the other night.
Yeah, I figured it's not the impression
you wanted to make during your interview.
(chuckling): No, definitely not.
Plus, if it got back to Teddy and Shane,
my whole family would start freaking out
that I wasn't being like
responsible Michaela.
Yeah.
Even though we were totally responsible.
Twice.
It's cool. I get it.
Uh. besides, Silver and
I have a complicated past,
and telling her I slept with her surrogate
might make things a
little more complicated.
- Found it.
- Oh, thank you.
Oh, there is an amazing
organic smoothie place
right down the street. I
think you're going to love it.
You want to come?
Sounds extra super,
but I've got to make
it to my calculus final.
You two ladies have a great day.
- Yeah, good luck.
- Bye.
See ya.
(phone buzzes)
(sighs)
Okay, Naomi, I got your emergency text.
It better be bigger than a shoe sale,
because I have a lot going on right now.
Annie, this is Mark Holland. (giggles)
He owns a food truck.
I told him how we need his
help planning a massive party.
We do?
I was a little surprised, too.
I appreciate you considering me,
it's just, I own a taco truck.
I'm still not clear who gave you my number.
Annie and I have a half-brother
who was given up for
adoption before we were born.
Her father seduced my mother
at a high school dance,
and the rest is sordid family history.
Which you just shared
with a total stranger.
And we need your help
planning a celebration
to welcome him back into our lives.
Uh, no, we don't.
It's time.
Don't you remember what
happened the last time
a half-brother came into our lives?
He stole money from your mother
and almost ruined our friendship.
That was completely
different; he was an impostor.
You know what?
Why don't you guys talk privately,
figure out what you want,
and if it ends up being a taco truck,
give me a call.
I don't know what got this into your head,
but it is a horrible idea.
What makes you think you
can even find this person
in the first place?
Because I already did. He's right here?
Oh, hi.
Why are you both looking at me?
He's our half-brother?
Surprise!
Welcome to our family.
(theme music playing)
- synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -
I can't believe you would go looking
for our half-brother without
talking to me first, Naomi.
How could you do something like this?
I hired a P.I.
You hired someone to find me?
I am so sorry.
My divorce from Max left a hole in my life,
one that I would usually fill by
jumping in bed with the next man I met.
But I am trying to evolve.
So, I need a deeply personal,
yet non-sexual relationship...
like you have with Dixon...
hence, I found my brother.
So, is there a job or not?
No, I made that up to bring you here.
All right then, take it easy.
You're leaving?
You don't want to know about...
me... about your family?
I already know about my family:
they're the people who raised me.
The non-sexual hole you're looking to fill
really isn't my problem.
Now, if you'd excuse me,
I have a business to run.
I can't believe he just walked out.
Like this?
He's your brother, too, Annie.
And his temper clearly comes
from your side of the family.
(sighs)
You went shopping, you
wonderful woman, you.
What the heck is "spelt"?
A whole grain.
And, for the record,
all of this food is for Michaela only.
All of it?
Which reminds me,
here's Michaela's first month's rent check
from me and Teddy.
Look, I... I hope giving
your surrogate a room
kind of makes up for the time
I implied that you weren't
ready to be a mother.
(sighs)
You're really helping us out
giving us a good deal on rent,
but, feel free to keep apologizing.
Dixon, your place is amazing.
Thanks.
God, look at that ocean.
Hey, do you think you
could teach me how to surf?
Oh, that's probably not going to happen.
I mean, the water's, like,
really polluted and, uh...
those guys out there take
really big falls, so...
It's pretty safe, actually.
But, I wouldn't even
have the time to show you.
It's crazy.
Actually, I've got to make my way down
to the Offshore right now.
Annie says she has a big surprise for me.
Hopefully, it's a trust
fund that I don't know about.
See you guys later.
I actually have a surprise for you, too.
Nothing exciting, but...
some books on pregnancy!
Oh...
What to eat, what not
to eat, the whole thing.
And I signed us up for yoga tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Yeah. Why, do you have something going on?
Oh, no, I mean, I just thought since we
spent the last few days
shopping for course materials
and prenatal vitamins,
maybe I could have tomorrow off?
I don't really know what you mean by off.
I mean, you're having my baby.
It's not like a nine-to-five job
you can just punch a clock.
Right. So, yoga tomorrow then?
Yes, that would be awesome.
I think you're going to love it.
Yeah.
Fun, fun, fun.
Oh. Psst!
Campbell, hey. Dude.
Hey, what's up?
Hey, uh, are you out of your mind?
Why did you text me
those answers yesterday?
I was doing fine on that test.
Navid, it's no big deal, all right?
It's just a little something we do for
for our Cronus Society
members to keep our grades up.
Besides, you didn't have to use the answers
if you didn't want to.
Yeah, uh... (quietly): I couldn't help it.
Okay, once I saw them
scrolling across my phone,
I couldn't get them out of my head.
Great, so you did a little better
than you would have otherwise.
Nobody got hurt.
Now you can return the favor.
- Favor?
- Yeah.
What... what do you mean?
Our physics final is coming up.
You've aced every test this semester.
So, once you figure out the answers
just text them to the rest of the guys.
Yeah, uh...
I... I can't do that.
Accepting help for something
I didn't ask for was one thing,
but people get kicked out of school
for this kind of stuff.
Hmm. Fine.
Then you're out of Cronus.
Are... are you serious?
Yeah.
And since you know about
our little arrangement,
we're going to have to kill you.
Dude... I'm kidding.
All right, loosen up.
Yeah, of course you are.
It's not that big of a deal.
We'll just get somebody else to do it.
Really?
- Yeah.
- All right.
It takes a lot of guts to
stand up for your convictions
instead of help out your friends.
I admire that.
I'll see you at the Frolic, right?
Yeah, absolutely.
- All right, see ya, bud.
- Yeah, see ya.
(sighs)
I can't believe my sister
took over a college Battle of
the Bands to find me clients.
This officially makes me the
worst music producer in history.
No, it doesn't.
New artists are discovered
this way all the time.
They found Justin Bieber on the Internet.
Do you know how many dancing babies
and weirdly talented
cats you got to go through
just to find something like that?
This is going to be easy.
As my talent coordinator,
you get V.I.P. access to all the bands.
With any luck, you'll find
someone you'll want to sign,
your music label will be back in business,
and you can finally stop stressing.
Start listening to demos.
Annie, hi. Have you seen Liam?
I need to talk to him
about renting the Offshore
to start a restaurant.
This has something to
do with Mark, doesn't it?
Our brother who sells
food out of a truck? No.
Naomi.
Okay, look, I realize that
my little stunt yesterday
backfired, so I'm turning to plan B.
If Mark doesn't have time
for me in his private life,
I will buy a restaurant and be a part
of his professional one.
Well, in case you've forgotten,
I already have a brother.
And Dixon's already under
a huge amount of pressure
after losing Ade from
his record label, okay?
Last time a half-brother showed
up, he completely flipped out.
He doesn't need this right
now, and neither do I.
Uh-huh, what about Mark?
You saw how cute and middle-class he was.
He needs me in his life.
Okay, you can't just
take over people's lives
and fix them, Naomi. It doesn't work.
Hey, Annie, thanks for hooking this up.
Some of these bands are
actually pretty decent.
If you forcing me to do this contest
brings me back into this business,
I officially owe all of my
success to my beautiful sister.
(giggling)
Oh.
(laughs quietly)
Hi, kettle, I'm pot.
Nice to meet you.
(scoffs)
Okay, how does this sound?
Your Honor, I know that
I have made some mistakes,
and every since the incident,
my career has a taken a huge nosedive,
but throwing the book at me would be cruel
and unusual punishment.
You flashed a group of
people, you didn't rob a bank.
They'll probably just give you a warning.
That'd be great.
That way I could put
this huge mess behind me.
I can't wait to put this behind me either.
Sooner they put Ashley away,
the sooner I can start pretending
this whole kidnapping thing never happened.
Liam Court.
Yeah. That's me.
Wish me luck.
ASHLEY: Liam.
Liam, thank God you're here.
Everyone is so confused.
They don't understand I
was trying to protect you.
You have to tell them the truth.
Liam! Liam!
Are you okay?
Yeah, just got to get some water.
(breathing heavily)
Are you sure you're okay?
(grunts)
(choking)
Hey, get off of her.
Hey, why are you grabbing
me, she's the one who...
- Come on.
- Ade...
How's Ade?
Shaken but fine.
She's worried about you.
The court said they wouldn't release me
until I saw a medical professional.
Maybe they're right.
Maybe I do need help.
Adrianna told me what's going on with you.
The kidnapping, your friend's shooting.
Liam, have you been
having trouble sleeping?
Mood swings, anxiety?
No more than anyone else
who almost got shipped to Mexico in a box.
Liam, I think you are suffering
from post-traumatic stress disorder.
PTSD? It's not like I went to war.
Combat isn't the only cause,
but treatment's pretty standard.
(sighs) Cognitive behavior therapy.
You need to confront the things
that remind you of your trauma
and deal with what happened
instead of hiding from it.
So, you're saying I need to
do more of what I did today,
'Cause that worked out great.
Confronting your past
is the only way to start feeling better.
Don't take this the wrong
way, but that sounds crazy.
(sighs)
Are we done here?
Hello. Welcome to C.U.'s First Annual
Food Truck Competition.
Wait, you work here?
If by work here you mean,
created the entire contest,
then yes.
What are you doing?
I already wasted half my day yesterday
with your fake catering job.
I think I'll pass on
the pretend food contest.
Oh, so I guess it doesn't matter
that Wolfgang Puck is judging?
The Wolfgang Puck?
Such a charming man.
I mean, he single-handedly changed
the face of American cuisine.
The guy's amazing.
He started with nothing
and created an empire.
You could do the same thing
if you win the contest.
First prize is a write-up from Wolfgang,
plus a silent partner will help you
open up your own restaurant at
this amazing waterfront location.
But if you prefer selling tacos
to tourists at the tar pits,
then by all means, fly free.
Okay, fine, I'll do the contest.
But just so we're clear,
I'm doing this to help my business.
Don't think it means we're taking
family vacations together.
Adrianna.
Oh, hey. Hi.
Look, I just wanted to
apologize again for yesterday.
It's fine.
- You didn't realize it was me.
- Yeah.
So, did you talk to that therapist?
Yeah. But she's clueless.
She keeps trying to talk me into
some kind of stupid treatment.
But, Liam, if you don't get help,
how do you know this isn't
going to happen again?
Okay, let's-let's make a deal.
Once you fix your own life,
then you can tell me how to run mine.
Didn't I meet you at a bar somewhere?
I didn't know you were going to be here.
Where's Silver?
Not here.
I needed a break, so I got away.
And since there's not a baby
supply store within sight,
- I think we're safe.
- Ah.
You feel like hanging out?
Sure, yeah.
Who's to say we didn't, uh,
just bump into each other?
And decided to catch a little music.
Awesome.
So, I'm going to get some food
that doesn't contain any healthy fiber.
I'll see you in five.
Okay.
So... looks like you totally hooked up
with that girl from the bar the
other night and didn't tell us.
Ah, she's... she's a nice girl.
- I didn't want to make a big deal.
- Mm-hmm.
And if her boss found out it
could cause a lot of problems.
Hey, so can you do me a favor,
and just keep this between us?
You want me to lie to the
guys about what I just saw?
I'm starting to see some cracks
in that moral code of yours.
But, hey, your secret's safe with me.
I mean, that's what
Cronus is all about, right?
Friends helping each other out.
All right, I got to go man, I'll see ya.
See ya.
Man, this is probably the best taco
I've ever had in my life.
And I'm not just saying that because
- I've been working since 8:00.
- Thanks.
This event's actually turning
into huge business for me.
Yeah, well, hopefully for me, too.
Running this contest was my sister's idea,
and it's actually turning
out to be a pretty good one.
You know what?
I kind of got dragged
into this the same way.
But I'm having a blast.
- I... I... I'm Mark.
- Dixon.
Good to meet you, man.
Uh, what are you doing here?
I'm getting a taco.
Mark, this is my sister, Annie.
Wait, she's your sister?
And Dixon is my one and only brother.
If you know what I mean?
I don't.
Look, I'm just here to win
Naomi's food truck contest.
Wait, this whole contest was Naomi's idea?
Yeah, I didn't realize throwing contests
for your relatives was a family tradition.
So, you guys know each other
and you know Naomi?
We shouldn't hold the line up.
Uh, we would love to stick around and chat
but Dixon and I have a lot to do right now
and I'm sure you do, too.
It was nice meeting you. Bye.
♪
♪ Now, baby, I ♪
♪ Was just travelin' by ♪
♪ When you roped me in
then you knocked me out ♪
♪ And, baby, you ♪
♪ You try to confuse... ♪
Excuse me.
Aren't you Adrianna Tate-Duncan?
Yeah.
My band is supposed to be
on stage in five minutes,
and we lost our lead singer.
Now I know this is going to sound crazy,
but is there any chance you'd
consider performing with us?
You want me to sing?
Yeah, we're huge fans,
lyrics are super easy,
and you would totally be saving our ass.
You know what, sure, why not?
Awesome. The guys are gonna flip.
Come on. (laughs)
Wolfgang, thanks again for coming.
You have turned our little contest
into an enormous success.
I love helping young chefs get
the recognition they deserve.
How are you finding the food?
Anyone in particular
standing out in your mind?
As a matter of fact,
the taco truck over there is fantastic.
You know, I'm completely impartial,
but they're my favorite, too. (laughs)
Right now, he's in first place
with this crepe truck over here.
Oh, tied?
Yeah, maybe I have to
go for another tasting.
That's an excellent idea. (laughs)
But first, do you want
to go cleanse your palate
over at the beer garden?
You can tell them Naomi sent you.
Thanks.
Mmm. Peppers.
Careful, these jalapeños
are painfully spicy.
Everyone is loving your tacos,
but... the contest isn't over yet.
So, if you have any tricks up your sleeve,
you might want to whip them out now.
What kind of tricks?
Oh, I don't know, a
secret sauce or something.
This is pretty much what I do.
Well, you don't want
anything getting in the way
of opening up your restaurant.
Besides, if you're anything like me,
you want to crush the competition.
Well, then, I guess I'm
not anything like you.
I got to get back to work.
Hey, Ade.
Look, I really need your help.
Um, I'm kind of trying to learn this song.
Can it wait? This is, like,
an emergency, all right?
Michaela, she bailed on yoga class.
Now I can't find her anywhere.
Oh, my God, seriously?
- What? This is important.
- Yeah, like,
way more important than anything
going on in my life right now.
Like the fact that I'm
about to get on stage
with a band that I just
met five minutes ago.
Or how about yesterday,
when I was in court with Liam
and he tried to strangle me?
What?
Liam tried to strangle you?
(scoffs) You know what?
Don't even worry about it.
It doesn't affect your life,
so it's not important, right?
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have to go try and save my career.
♪
Well, that band was pretty interesting.
Yeah. Uh, not as interesting
as what just happened at the food truck.
Dixon, nothing was going on.
I just needed to get you back here.
I mean, I didn't put on this whole contest
so you could stand around
chatting with some taco guy.
Well, he seemed like he was
more than just some taco guy.
He wasn't.
Annie, come on.
We're grown, okay?
You can tell me the truth.
What, did you sleep with him or something?
Ew, Dixon. No.
Okay, fine. If you won't tell me,
then I know Naomi will.
Okay.
Okay, look.
He is not just the taco guy.
He's our half-brother.
He's our what?
Naomi tracked him down.
She insists that she
needs family in her life,
but I told her I didn't want
- any part of it.
- And you weren't gonna tell me?
I was trying to protect you.
The last time I saw you this stressed out,
you ended up in rehab, okay? So...
I don't care what Naomi needs in her life,
because I need you in mine.
You're my brother, not him.
I admit things aren't
great for me right now,
but there's nothing that's
gonna put me back on drugs.
How can you be so sure of that?
Because I have a 12-step program.
Because I have you.
A crazy-ass sister who's
always gonna be there for me.
So, I totally understand why Naomi would
need something like that in her life.
I just worry about you, you know?
I know, I know.
But, uh, like it or not,
I'm not your only brother anymore.
(applause)
(shrieks): We won!
You won. All you.
Congratulations, Mark.
Your tacos were some of
the best I have ever tasted.
You have no idea what that means to me.
Honestly, when I saw the crepe truck,
I didn't think I could win.
That guy does some great work.
I thought so, too.
But after my second tasting,
then he put something crazy in his batter.
It tasted like jalapenos.
I'm sorry, did you say "jalapenos"?
Mark, you might want to
pose for the cameras here.
Okay.
What? What?
(speaking German)
Uh, Mark? (laughs)
NAOMI: Where are you going?
You can't just walk
away from Wolfgang Puck.
You sabotaged another chef's food
so I'd win some contest?
What kind of person does that?
I needed you to win.
I wasn't going to open a restaurant
with Mr. Flirty Crepe Maker.
The silent partner with the
amazing waterfront space is you?
Mark...
You're insane.
(Naomi sighs)
(engine starts)
(grunts)
♪
Hey, C.U.!
You guys ready to rock?
(Adrianna whoops)
♪ I'm ready to go ♪
♪ Yeah, I'm ready to go ♪
♪ I'm ready to go oh-oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ I'm ready to go ♪
♪ Got my eyes on the road ♪
♪ Hold me back, girls ♪
♪ Yes, I'm ready to go... ♪
(grunts)
♪ If you see me ♪
♪ Make believe I'll go ♪
(hissing)
♪ Come on ♪
♪ Keep on moving ♪
♪ Pushing through, yeah ♪
♪ I'm ready to go ♪
♪ Yeah, I'm ready to go... ♪
Liam.
Ade told me what happened yesterday.
I really don't want to talk about it.
I'm just here to listen to some music
and grab a beer while Navid's buying.
♪ When you feel it ♪
Michaela!
I've been calling you
and looking for you...
Are you drinking beer?
No, the... the beer's mine.
Uh, don't worry about it,
I just gave her a little taste.
So, what, y... you bail on yoga
so you can come and party?
I just needed a break. All right?
I mean, I thought about telling you,
but I didn't want you wigging out.
I'm not pregnant yet.
I think it's cool if I have a beer.
MAN: Come on...
let the girl have a drink, you know?
Maybe Navid'll get lucky again.
Okay, what the hell is
this guy talking about?
He's drunk, just ignore him.
Are you seriously telling me, man,
that you didn't bag this chick... No.
At that bar last weekend?
Because the official Cronus
position, uh, is that you did.
You know what, buddy?
I think it's time for you to shut up.
Wait. Did you guys hook up?
- Silver, it's not what you think.
- MICHAELA: Oh, my God, screw this.
I don't care if Shane
and the rest of my family
think I'm like the Whore of Babylon.
Navid and I hooked up.
All right? And who knows,
- maybe we'll do it again.
- Hey, dude.
What's your problem, man?
My problem is everyone
asking me what my problem is.
(crowd gasps)
Liam, what are you doing?
I got to get some air.
(grunts) Hey!
Seriously?
You have to give me a chance to fix this.
Being adopted doesn't make me an orphan.
And it doesn't make you my Daddy Warbucks.
I was fine before you came into my life.
Yes, well, maybe I wasn't, okay?
In case you haven't noticed,
my life is kind of a mess right now.
I... I just... I really need my brother.
I'm not your brother.
And I don't even know you.
Fire!
(tires squeal)
(Naomi screams, Mark grunts)
Liam, wait, where we going, man?
(screams in distance)
(screams)
Hey, that's the guy that punched me.
His name's Liam Court,
and I want you to arrest his ass.
Sir, you're gonna need to come with us.
You got to be kidding me.
Mark?
I'm sorry.
(Naomi sighs)
Is she gonna be okay?
Hey, guys.
I'm really sorry this didn't work out.
We were killing it up there.
But who knows?
Maybe we'll still win.
You know, honestly?
We thought you'd put a little bit
more into your performance.
You know, rip your top off like
you did at the charity event.
But I thought you liked my singing. I do.
But I said we were fans of your work,
which includes showing
a little something extra.
It's kind of what you're known for.
You're here.
I wasn't sure where you were going.
Maybe you should put a
tracking device in my car.
(laughs) I'm sorry,
I just can't believe that you
slept with Navid and didn't tell me.
Well, I can't believe you think it's okay
to dictate my behavior
for the next nine months.
It's a baby, Silver.
People have them all the time.
Yeah, but this is my baby, okay?
And since I can't carry it myself,
I'm paying you to be responsible
and take it seriously.
All right, look.
I know this is weird for you,
because it's really weird for me, too.
I had a vision for how
my pregnancy would go,
and it most definitely did
not involve a surrogate.
So, everything that I was
planning on doing for my baby, I...
I have to do through you.
Does that make sense?
Yeah, it does.
But you spend so much time
obsessing over this baby
that you don't have time for anything else.
Not a relationship, not school,
not even your friends.
- I just want everything to be perfect.
- And is it?
Take it from me.
From somebody whose family
is completely over-involved
and controlling.
It's not healthy.
Not for you, and
certainly not for the baby.
Hey, Josh.
Hey, Campbell, uh,
do... do you have a second?
Man, I'm sorry Simon outed you
and that girl to all your friends.
Kid's got a big mouth.
But Liam really laid him out, huh?
Hope he doesn't get into a ton of trouble.
Yeah, well, I guess it
all depends on Simon.
Yup. He's a... he's a Cronus guy, right?
Mm-hmm.
Is there any way that you could talk to him
and convince him to let the whole thing go?
Wait a second, you're seriously asking me
to bend the rules for you again?
Because I thought you had
a whole thing about that.
Well, no, this is different.
Okay, uh, Liam's a good friend of mine,
and, uh, he could really use my help.
No, I get it, I really do.
It just... it seems a little unfair
if you're not willing to
return the favor, you know?
The offer's still on the table.
See you at the physics
final tomorrow, all right?
- Yeah.
- All right, buddy.
Hey.
I wanted to come and check on you.
(sighs)
Dixon found out about Mark,
and he was okay with it.
Turns out I don't need to worry
about him as much as I thought.
Are you gonna be okay?
I managed to screw up every
meaningful relationship
I've ever had in my life, but...
my, uh, husband, my sister,
my parents, everybody.
(chuckles)
It's okay.
I just wanted someone
to share a bond with me
that we couldn't walk away from, you know?
Something like you have with Dixon.
No matter what happens,
you always have each other.
You're his something.
And that's, uh...
something I may never have.
You don't know that.
Since I don't have any more
half-siblings out there, I...
Well, I figure,
Mark was my last shot.
That is one messed-up food truck.
Look, if Naomi sent you to
make some kind of sales pitch,
you can save your breath.
I don't want anything to do
with her or your crazy family.
I totally get that.
When I found out about
you, I felt the same way.
I kind of got the feeling
you didn't like me.
Yeah, well, family can
be a huge pain in the ass.
I recently figured that out.
So I'm guessing you don't
have any brothers or sisters?
My parents adopted me because
they couldn't have kids.
- I gave them so much trouble, they didn't want more.
- Oh.
My family adopted Dixon when we were eight.
And even though it hasn't always been easy,
it's really nice knowing
there's someone there
who loves you and has your back.
But maybe you have enough
people in your life like that already,
in which case, congratulations.
Anyway, Naomi wanted me to
swing by and give you this.
She wants to take the truck off your hands
so you can buy a new one.
She didn't have to do that.
You're right.
She didn't.
(sighs)
- Hey.
- Mm.
Hey, is, uh... is everything okay?
Yeah, it will be.
That kid that I hit yesterday
decided not to press charges,
so I'm off the hook.
No way. Hey, that's... that's fantastic.
Yeah. I could have really
hurt that guy, though...
or Ade.
I realized that I just
can't keep pretending
like nothing's wrong.
Yeah. So, uh, what are you gonna do?
Well, according to my
court-appointed therapist,
the first step is confronting
what happened to me,
so... that's what I'm doing.
You're not going to kill someone
with a screwdriver, are you?
No.
(chuckles quietly)
Oh, uh, by the way, I ran into Campbell.
He wanted me to give you these.
Lakers tickets, court side.
He said, uh, some of the guys
were going out to celebrate
a physics test they aced?
Oh.
Awesome.
I got your text.
What's wrong? Michaela
ran out of flaxseed oil?
(sighs)
Okay, I totally deserve that.
Look, I've been a terrible friend lately.
(sighs)
I've been self-centered,
and I've been totally
obsessed with this baby thing.
I'm sorry. I miss you.
I've really missed you, too.
I'm not saying I won't still
occasionally check in on Michaela,
or go a little baby-crazy,
but I'm gonna try to
have a normal life again.
You know, like, turn over a new leaf.
I'm turning over a new leaf, too.
That wardrobe malfunction
is going to follow me around
as long as I'm in the spotlight.
So I've decided to take some
time off from my singing career.
That might be the best
news I've ever heard,
because I talked Naomi into letting me have
her brother's old food truck.
What are you going to
do, sell burritos, or... ?
No, 'cause the kitchen's shot.
But I figured...
we can come up with something creative.
We could do something awesome.
If you want to be my partner.
Oh, my God!
These are adorable! I love them!
- Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yes.
- Yes!
(laughs) Gonna be awesome!
Yup.
Yes!
(laughter)
(doorbell rings) Ow. Oh.
Come in!
(footsteps approaching)
Annie didn't give you my check?
She did. I'm gonna make this short.
I've always felt like I
had a pretty full life,
and then you swooped in and...
obviously need me.
(sighs) I'm not a charity case.
I can order in.
Oh, and waste such a beautiful kitchen?
gives me an excuse
Losing my truck to do something
I've wanted to do for a long time.
And even without your jalapenos,
I'm pretty sure I would have
kicked that fake Frenchie's butt.
So...
you still interested in
opening that restaurant?
Are you serious?
A few rules. You leave the cooking to me,
and no more surprises. Deal?
Deal. I'm a horrible cook.
I'll drop by tomorrow.
You can show me this
amazing waterfront place.
Oh.
I'll see you later... sis.
(footsteps retreating)
(rock music plays on computer)
(indistinct rock plays on
computer) * I once was lost *
♪ But now I'm found ♪
♪ Was blind, but now I see. ♪
Oh.
I'm sorry. I didn't know you were here.
No, no, no, don't...
don't... don't apologize.
That was... that was actually pretty great.
Too bad I didn't find anyone like you
at that contest yesterday.
What do you mean?
I own a music label,
and I was there looking for new talent.
Um, someone I could turn into a star.
It was a complete wash, but
you know, it's okay. I'll be fine.
I'm sorry, can we go back to the part
about you owning a music label?
Are you saying you could make me a star?
I have to say,
I'm happy someone finally
decided to rent this space.
It's been empty for a long time.
So, what are you going to do with it?
I don't know.
Uh, I decided it was time
to start looking towards the future,
and this seemed like
the right place to start.
Well, good luck.
Thank you.
ASHLEY: You'll be traveling in this.
LIAM: You're gonna put me in a box?
ASHLEY: Just long enough to
ship you to Southern Mexico.
LIAM: You're insane.
ASHLEY: I'm not insane.
I'm doing this for you.